<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Auke Rijpma</title>
    <link>https://www.aukerijpma.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Auke Rijpma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:24 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aukerijpma.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>https://www.aukerijpma.nl/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aukerijpma.nl/data/</guid>
      <description>Data Openarch deaths  Cleaned, deduplicated and (partially) standardized version of Dutch death certificates (c. 1811-1960), retrieved from openarch.nl. The csv files per archive, used to create this dataset, were retrieved in January 2020. Scripts used to create this dataset are available at github/wp4-civreg (version 1.0). Repository  Church construction data  A dataset on church construction in Western Europe, 700–1500, based on OpenStreetMap. 🗺 ⛪ Licence (following the OSM source licence).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links and projects</title>
      <link>https://www.aukerijpma.nl/link/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aukerijpma.nl/link/</guid>
      <description> Clariah project Clariah Structured Data Hub/DataLegend Clio-Infra IISH Historical Prices and Wages Cape of Good Hope Panel R ❤️ r-data.table Github openarch  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.aukerijpma.nl/pub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aukerijpma.nl/pub/</guid>
      <description>Publications Auke Rijpma, Ingrid K. van Dijk, Ruben Schalk, Richard L. Zijdeman, and Rick J. Mourits (2022), &amp;ldquo;Unequal excess mortality during the Spanish Flu pandemic&amp;rdquo;. Econmoics and human biology, forthcoming.
Van Bavel, Bas, Sjoerd Hardeman, Robin Philips, Auke Rijpma, Erik Stam, and Jan Luiten Van Zanden. 2022. “Capaciteitenbenadering Biedt Goede Basis Voor Meten van Welvaart.” Economisch Statistische Berichten. https://esb.nu/esb/20069497/capaciteitenbenadering-biedt-goede-basis-voor-meten-van-welvaart.
de Zwart, Pim, Daniel Gallardo-Albarrán, and Auke Rijpma. 2021. “The Demographic Effects of Colonialism: Forced Labor and Mortality in Java, 1834–1879.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working papers</title>
      <link>https://www.aukerijpma.nl/wp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aukerijpma.nl/wp/</guid>
      <description>Working papers Ruben Schalk and Auke Rijpma (2019). “Migration for necessity or proficiency: The Netherlands, 1750-1920”.
Auke Rijpma, Jan Luiten van Zanden, and Marco Mira d’Ercole (2018). “A Long-Term Perspective on the Development Experience of Emerging and Industrialised Economies”. OECD Statistics Working Papers 2018/10.
Auke Rijpma (2016). “What Can’t Money Buy? Wellbeing and GDP since 1820”. Working Paper 0078. Utrecht University, Centre for Global Economic History.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
